What on earth!
Look at that!
It's closing in!
Isn't there anyone available?
We have word that Lightning Max
and Smile Man are on their way.
Get me the threat level assessment!
As you can see, loud explosions
are going off behind me!
The damage left by the monster
is at an unprecedented scale.
m 0 0 l 120 0 120 540 0 540
Huge explosions
in City A
m 0 0 l 1200 0 1200 50 0 50
City A sustains heavy destruction due to heavy explosions c
The Heroes Association is currently
analyzing the threat level—
Time to go.
JUSTICE
ENFORCEMENT
Daddy! Mommy!
And who you might be?
Just a guy who's a hero for fun.
What kind of...
...half-assed backstory is that?
I was formed from
the constant stream of pollution
with which you humans
have suffused the earth.
I am Vaccine Man!
The Earth is a single living organism.
You humans are nothing but
a disease-causing bacteria
eating away at her lifeforce.
In order to obliterate humans
and their evil civilization,
the Earth has given birth to me!
You say you do this for fun?
For fun?
How dare you confront me,
Mother Earth's apostle,
for that inane reason?!
Yet, what more could be
expected from a hu—
Not again...
All it took was one punch!
DAMN IT!
Shoutout to YouTubers :
[ Raito ], AnnieMay MissHurt  &   Isaiah Leblanc
One ponch!!!
Three, two, one, kiss Joe
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
Sir Joe, Kiss Joe, Shit Joe, Side Joe!
nan datten da, frustration
Massive glitter, Restoration?  ☻
ore wa tomaranai
What about tomorrow night?!!
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One ponch, can you make shit and let it show?
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
All of the cocks, too many cocks, Soooooo?
power, get power
Power, ghetto power
girigiri genkai made
Kitty Kitty, can you tie my DICK?
Key whore
ore o tataeru koe ya
Poor little duck, the heir of Korea
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
Cat's eye?, Nah. Take a shit through the night
He row!
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
The car, oh, take a shit in zoo,
the cool toe of the macau.
Never take a nap, Oh yeah!
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Soda, don't worry; Oh she oh sang with a Key!
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
Ole wah, still don't care, what? she high!
Kill rock!
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
The lava, to kill a key capture you shit, out away.
tatakau hero
The tech guy oh!  Key row
kodoku na hero
Color Cora Key Whore
I
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be a Psycho Hero!
THREE YEARS AGO
Fuu-Ku-Ku-Ku-Ku-Ku-Ku!
– A monster!
– Run!
Huh?
You sure you
don't want to run away?
I bet you're a newly employed
businessman already tired of work.
I ate too much crab and
transformed into this, Crablante!
Why aren't you running?
You've got a death wish.
Isn't that right?
Well, not quite.
I'm no businessman. I'm unemployed.
Right now, I'm looking for a job.
I had another interview today
and got rejected royally.
I couldn't care less about anything.
So I'm in no mood to run
just because the mighty
Crablante has appeared.
So, what'll happen if I don't run?
Your eyes are lifeless, just like mine.
From one set of lifeless eyes
to another, I'll let you go.
Besides, right now...
I'm hunting different prey.
A big-chinned brat.
And when I find him,
I'm gonna rip his arms off!
What're you looking at?
A big-chinned brat...
If he's caught, he'll definitely be killed!
Hey, kid. Did you do anything
to a big crab monster earlier?
Huh?
He was asleep in the park,
so I drew some nipples on him.
It's definitely him...
He has no idea what he's done.
What do I do? I could still help...
But man, this kid isn't cute at all.
It's none of my business...
I should just walk away.
Right. I mean, who really cares anyway?
I found you!
What the hell am I doing?
Huh!
Kid, he's after you!
Hurry, get outta here!
Don't worry about me. Just go!
B-But...
My soccer ball...
Your ball?!
Hey you, what's the big idea?
Don't tell me you're gonna
protect that stinkin' brat!
Come on, you're gonna kill him
over some harmless prank?
Think about this!
I've already mutilated lots of people.
Whoever makes fun of
the way I look, pays the price.
By the way, that brat...
...drew nipples on my body.
With a permanent marker!
Look at these claws!
I can't even use a towel to wipe it off!
If you get in my way, I'll make sure
you never go job hunting again!
It just came to me.
You look exactly like a villain
from this anime I used to watch!
Die.
Hold it right there.
In this age of declining birth rates,
I can't just let you kill a kid.
You know what?
I've wanted to become a hero
ever since I was a little kid.
Not a businessman,
but a hero, who could kick
asses of villains like you.
Screw looking for a job!
Bring it on!
Some hero you are!
You're pathetic!
You don't stand
a chance against me.
Your life ends...now!
Has it really been three years since then?
After that day,
I trained so hard that I went bald.
I became so powerful,
no one can beat me.
I'm the hero I dreamed of becoming.
So what is this? What's wrong?
Why does my heart feel so empty?
482 yen, please.
Okay.
Oh, hang on.
I have 82 yen.
Incredible...
This is incredible, little brother!
I never thought it would work so well.
Yes, it's more than
I had ever imagined, big brother.
My goal was to become
the strongest man in the world.
The strongest man.
That was my dream.
At last, the ultimate steroid,
"Biceps King," is complete!
Little brother!
Drink this and you will obtain
the power you've been seeking!
Huh? Drink that?
Indeed! I added strawberry flavoring,
to make it go down easier.
Brother...
Yes, this will do!
My brains and your brawn!
By combining the greatest of minds
and the strongest of bodies,
we brothers will conquer everything
on earth
and rule as kings!
I-Incredible!
Well done, little brother.
Thousands have perished!
Now, on to the next town
to destroy it as well!
This! This is it, big bro.
This is what I was looking for...
To be the strongest man.
This is an emergency
evacuation warning.
A giant creature has
appeared in City D.
The creature is currently
heading towards City B.
All residents of the area,
please evacuate immediately.
I repeat, the giant creature
is currently heading for—
Yes, that's right! Scatter like rats!
Get them!
I'm the strongest man,
I'm the strongest.
I'm the strongest man.
What do you think, brother?
Yeah, how's it feel
being the strongest?
What?!
There's someone on your shoulder!
Put some pants on.
That guy on your shoulder! Kill him!
Brotherrrr!
How did this happen?!
I just wanted to be strong!
And I finally am
the strongest man, but...!
I don't know who you are,
but it's your fault my brother is dead!
The strongest!
Behold our brotherly power!
I am the strongest.
So what if I am?
I feel empty.
Right?
Having overwhelming strength is...
...pretty boring.
Oops.
CITY B DESTROYED
There's no sign that the evils
of the world are disappearing.
This hasn't changed since
before I became a hero.
In other words, you could say that
I haven't made any impact.
I'm not necessarily sad about that.
But there's something
bothering me lately.
As the days pass,
my emotions grow more distant.
Fear, tension, joy, anger...
I feel none of them anymore.
In exchange for power,
maybe I've lost something
that's essential for a human being!
Vroom, vroom?
No sense hiding if you saw me.
I'm Super Custom YO649Z Mk. II!
I love...
– building custom cars so much...
– I used to feel all kinds of emotions
– I decked myself out.
– whirling inside me when I fought.
– I'm a custom car-loving monster!
– Fear. Panic. Anger.
If you're thinking of getting in my way,
I'll put a shine on
that big headlight of yours!
But now...
all I need is one punch to end it.
Guess I'll have eggs over rice tonight.
Each day...
I come home uninjured
and wash my gloves.
When I'm out fighting monsters...
I never feel as if my heart's really in it.
I mean, I just do the
hero-thing as a hobby.
In other words,
as long as I get a kick out of it,
that's all I care about.
My house?!
He's tough!
What the hell are you?
"What" am I? That's rude.
We are the true earthlings.
We?
I believe you call us
"Subterraneans."
We suffer from overpopulation.
Therefore, we must now
claim the world above ground.
I understand that there are
many people on the surface too.
As it stands, you are in our way.
That is why we have decided
to eradicate you all.
Since our invasion commenced,
70% of the surface dwellers
have been killed.
This is a battle for survival.
I hope you can understand that.
However, this is unexpected.
We have encountered
no surface dwellers
whom our punches would not kill.
I'd like to state the same.
It's been too long since
I've come across such worthy opponents,
Subterraneans!
We are earthlings!
But how?!
You bastard!
Die!
It's over.
What was that surface dweller?
I'm...
just a guy who's a hero for fun.
I cannot lose!
And the surface...
is under my protection!
Big talk for a race of vermin!
What is this feeling?
This wild throbbing in my heart?!
This rush,
this tension!
It's been so long, I forgot...
...the...
...exhilaration of a real fight!
I see.
It's coming back to me.
This is it.
Well, well...
Looks like you've been taking
good care of my children.
This is it!
I, the Subterranean King,
will take you on.
This is the very feeling...
...I've been looking for!
The surface is ours!
You surface dwellers must die!
I am the Subterranean King!
Surface dwellers,
prepare yourselves for—
All right, bring it on!
Sorry about that
I've become too strong.
THE
STRONGEST MAN
Hey, come back home soon
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
I close my eyes and think of you
I want to see you... I feel like crying
I feel so romantic
I hope these feelings reach you
I know very well
how hard you work all the time
You're the one I love
You're so strong but I'm still worried
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
I'll find you before any stars
Come straight back home
Hey, come back home soon
NEXT
EPISODE
THE LONE CYBORG
NEXT
EPISODE
THE LONE CYBORG
How'd you like seeing me this week?
Now it's time for me,
the mighty Crablante,
to tell you what happens next week.
Huh? There are no visuals?
Well, next week this guy appears
in Z City where Saitama lives!
What now? Time's up?
Well next week will be episode 2,
"The Lone Cyborg."
I hope you all—